coffee, there
our bro,
all at once.
Juninho what did you do?
it's doing business.
thursday
it's online bro,
non-human,
and then my partner?
car is clean,
revised engine,
full tank.
when my father died,
I remember the first thing I did was
thank God for the time I had with him.
I know it's hard,
but when you learn to be grateful for things
when they are
and not be moaning when they have to go.
everything in life is fleeting,
just like you.
your work,
his home,
your dog,
your car.
nothing lasts forever.
and today the one leaving is the chevas.
show you then,
like this,
oh then you have a good little step,
it's not even bad.
moaning things won't solve anything,
the truth will only make them a little more difficult.
accepting is freedom.
i have more peace when i choose to live this way.
Valeu mano,
success there,
tamo together
as well as chevas.
this workshop here
it's just a way to reach my goal
to open my business,
but that you will only find out
at the end of the series.